Hứa Hoàng Thanh Bảo

Web Developer

Contact information

Phone 0908-432-264

E-Mail huahoangthanhbao@gmail.com

Github https://github.com/HuaHoangThanhBao/

Blog https://uniodev.com/



Summary

I am a junior web developer with 1 year of experience for an international service company. My greatest strength is planning and problem solving, which enables me to reduce time and make work better. Also, I willing to learn new things.

Experience

09/2020 - present Web Developer

Doslink Group

- Responsible for maintaining, reducing loading time of company's websites.
- Implemented and upgraded new functions for website.
- Created chatbot service for facebook to increase user experience.
- Designed and built new websites with Wordpress. Edit plugin to be compatible with Wordpress environment.
- Integrated SMS OTP Verification system via phone number to collect data from customers.

05/2020 - 07/2020

Fresher Mobile Application

Sajbernet Company

- Learned to create mobile app using React Native framework.
- Fixed bug for old applications.

Education

09/2016 - 09/2020

Software Engineering

Graduated Huflit university

Skills

Front-end

- Designing UI using HTML, CSS3, SCSS to make responsive.
- Javascript skill to improve website functions.
- Familiar with Angular framework.

Backend

- Familiar with Asp.net MVC 5, Asp.net Core 2.0.
- Writing trigger and store procedure.
- Worked with ORM using Entity Framework.
- Knowlege about web api, restful api.

Git

- Used Git to control code version.

Communication

- Nicely work with large team.
- Basic English skills.

Projects

doslink.com.vn

(12/2020 - 01/2021)

Company	Doslink Group
Task	Integrate OTP sending system and optimize website
Members	1
Position	Web Developer
Description	 Reduced website's loading time from 10 second to 2 second, brought website to top 5 of Google Search. Coded new point test pages and integrated SMS OTP verification system to send OTP code via phone number.
Technology	Frontend: HTML, CSS, Javascript, JqueryBackend: PHP, MySQL Server

siqura.com.vn

(12/2020 - 02/2021)

Siqura International Trading (https://siqura.com.vn/)
Desgin and build landing page
3
Web Developer
Following instructions from leader.
Got designs from designing team, planning and coding menu, landing page and footer.
Integrated Facebook chat for website.
Frontend: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Jquery
Backend: PHP, MySQL Server
-

hangnhapkhauuc.vn

(02/2021 - Present)

Company	Samy Trading (https://hangnhapkhauuc.vn/)
Task	Building an e-commerce website
Members	3
Position	Web Developer
Description	 Redesign UI, optimize page's loading time. Implemented cart and checkout page. Building email notification system transfer data to company's sales system when a new order is placed. Connect to Integromate webhook to communicate with third party application. Integrated Facebook chat for website.
Technology	 Frontend: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Jquery Backend: PHP, MySQL Server

Certifications

09/2020 Software engineer certification

08/2020 TOEIC certification - 650pts